# **ATU PROSPER**

Software Engineer (Frontend)

### **PROFILE**

I am a smart-working Software Engineer (Frontend) with a flair for creating elegant and quality solutions in the possible least amount of time. I have over four (4) years of experience as a WordPress Developer and Graphics Designer. I have over two (2) years of experience building the web using React.JS, Next.JS and Gatsby.JS, and I have also done some backend development using ExpressJS and StrapiCMS.

I also write about my experience as I learn and build. I strive to follow best practices and use industry-standard tools, including Git-Flow, Test Driven Development, Continous Integration (Github Action), Linting (ESLint), Code Formatting (Prettier), Package Management (NPM) and Build Tool (Webpack).

## **EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2020 - Present (Remote)

#### **Metrovatech - Software Engineer**

- Develop Web apps using; HTML/CSS/JavaScript, React.js, Typescript, Graphql, REST, Strapi, WordPress...
- Design Graphical contents using; Photoshop. Illustrator, Corel Draw
- Train new employees

Dec 2018 - Jan 2020 (Full time)

#### Codelab Projects - WordPress Designer/Graphics Designer

- Designing of flyers and other printable materials
- Design wordpress websites for clients

Apr 2015 - Nov 2018 (Internship)

#### Telace Multimedia - Graphics Designer/Web Designer

- Graphics design and general branding.
- Web Design using WordPress.
- Customer Relationship Management.

#### **EDUCATION**

Nov 2011 - Aug 2016

Abia State Polytechnic, Aba

**HND - Computer Science** 

Thesis: Automate Customer Support System

Grade: AB (Very Good)

### **Hobbies**

Watch soccer





## **SKILLS**

HTML • CSS • Javascript • Go
React JS • Next JS • Gatsby JS
Node JS • Express JS • Firebase
Strapi • Typescript • Redux
GraphQL • REST API • Git • Jest
Wordpress • Material-UI
Corel Draw • Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop • Communication

# PROJECTS/PORTFOLIO

https://loctechng.com https://thetantalizersca.com https://surmountfoundation.org https://chappelledaycare.ca https://moorfieldoptometry.com.ng https://safe-haven-fe.vercel.app https://prosperatu.netlify.app https://prosper-blog.netlify.app

## **LANGUAGE**

English

## CERTIFICATION

ICSI | CNSS Certified Network Security Specialist ICSI (International CyberSecurity Institute), UK

Issued Jun 2020 · No Expiration Date

## **CURRENTLY**

- Enrolled in ALX software engineering program
- Learning Micro-services and gRPC

# **INTERESTS**

- Blockchain/Web3
- Cloud Computing
- Forex
- Politics
- Football

Watch comedy skits

